[{"answer": "Yes, ma'am, I'm on 2nd Avenue in the school and the gentleman said tell them to hold down the police officers are coming, he's going to start shooting.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "What's the address and your emergency?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Tell them to stop all movement.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I mean, that woman is a one-person crisis negotiating team and what is remarkable is that -- it's almost as if that was the role she was born to play on that particular day.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Martin, that really was quite remarkable to listen to, isn't it?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "No, school officials have not revealed a great deal about her.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Do we know anything else about her from the school or from anybody else?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, you know, unfortunately, Piers, we've had this conversation many times over the last year, and the answer is, it's going to be too many times.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "How many more times is this kind of thing going to happen before somebody somewhere takes action to try and stop at least some of it?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, it's horrific.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What is your reaction to that story?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "It's very, very difficult to do it.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How do you tackle this stream of disenfranchised, disaffected, perhaps deranged young -- they're usually white males who commit these mass shootings or have the intent to commit them?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is a lot of polarization here.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Sure, we have to keep up with the times and clearly social media is being used to change information, actually to show pictures of guns that were for sale.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Is that a new prong in your attack?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Wouldn't that make life easier for everyone in your kind of position as city police chief, just have the same rule in every state relating to guns?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Well I think a lot of people simply aren't affected by guns.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What is it about the gun itself, the culture of gun ownership, perhaps, which makes it so difficult to have this kind of sensible view of guns around the nation?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "No, it's certainly not racial profiling.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do you think stop-and-frisk is deliberate racial profiling but for a purpose that is, in your eyes, worth doing and successful?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "It's a story that's largely been blown up in the media and not exactly accurate.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Why is this?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "There is a lot of speculation.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Is that, as far as you know, true?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "We know that the relationship was that Jim played a very key role in the family and was seen as an uncle, obviously.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "But was she -- but, Andrew, was she aware, Laura, of any relationship between Christina Anderson and Jim DiMaggio?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you that I had a very close relationship with my daughter.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How did that make you feel, the collective pressure that she was clearly being put under?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "If anything, I think you need to keep tabs on your children's activity on the Internet.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "What is the lesson, the warning do you think to other parents that comes out of this awful tragedy?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Well, civilly we intend to prove that the actions of these young men and young woman was a main factor why Audrie did what she did, and civilly, we intend to prove that those actions did lead to her death.", "docId": "130821pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Bob Allard, in terms of the law surrounding all this, what are the issues that have been raised and does the law do enough do you think in situations like this?", "qSentId": 626}]